Guide to the Preservation Pittsburgh Records, 1985-2005 AIS.2005.03
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Project and Relevant Organization Files, 1981-1998; 1992-1998; III.
  - East Carson Street Historic Designation, South Side Local Development Company, 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - East Liberty Development Company, 1992-1994 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Freeman, Peggy Pierce, Pennsylvania Historical and Museum Commission, Mary Cardwell and the National Negro Opera Company, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Friends of the Riverfront, 1992-1997 (Box 4, Folder 50-51)
  - Highland Park Reservoir, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - The Hill District, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Historical Architectural Review Board, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Historical Society of Western Pennsylvania (Heinz History Center), 1991, 1993-1996 (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Holland, Dan, Board Member of Pittsburgh Community Reinvestment Group (PCRG), 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Hussey, Thomas L., University of Pittsburgh, 1992-1996 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - King's Estate Garden Party, 1990-1993 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Longhill Property, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Lowe, Stanley, correspondence on "Sacred Places", 1994 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Lubetz, Arthur, 1994-1997 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Lubove, Roy, Pittsburgh Historian, death, 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Market Square, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Moorewood-Shadyside Civic Association, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Neighborhood Groups and Organization Advocacy, 1991-1992 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Neill Log Cabin, Ad Hoc Committee, copies of historical and secondary sources to compile final report of legal status of the building, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 11-12)
  - Neill Log Cabin, Ad Hoc Committee to Organize Harvard-Yale-Princeton Club tour, 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Neill Log Cabin, Background research, possible project, 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Neill Log Cabin, Copies of historical documents, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Neill Log Cabin, Restoration, public advocacy and Preservation Pittsburgh Ad Hoc Committee efforts and research, 1993-1996 (Box 5, Folder 16-18)
  - Oakland Civic Historic District, 1991-1994 (Box 5, Folder 19-21)
  - Oakland Community Council, 1993-1997 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Oakland Directions, Inc., including by-laws, membership and officers, 1991-1992 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Oakland Neighborhood Alliance, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Oakland Neighborhood Conservation Association, 1981-1985 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Oakland Planning and Development Corporation, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Page, David, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Pennsylvania Historical and Museum Commission, Bureau for Historic Preservation, Key 93, 1992-1995 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Penzer, Richard, developer, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Philadelphia Historical Commission, Appellate Supreme Court of Pennsylvania Eastern District reverses decision against, 1988-1991 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Phipps Conservatory, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Pittsburgh Archaeology and History, Committee on, 1992-1995 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Pittsburgh Athletic Association, 1991-1992 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Pittsburgh Community Reinvestment Group, 1994-1995 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Pittsburgh Department of City Planning, 1991-1995 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Pittsburgh Downtown Partnership, 1994-1995 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Pittsburgh Founders Council, 1992-1994 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Pittsburgh History & Landmarks Foundation, 1992-1997 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Pittsburgh & Pennsylvania Historical Organizations, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Preservation Coalition of Greater Philadelphia, resume of Howard Kittell, Executive Director, 1989-1994 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Preservation Pittsburgh awarded an outstanding community service award by The Observer, 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Preservation Pennsylvania, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Preservation Pennsylvania, reports, 1991-1995 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Regional Resources, Inc., 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Saint Mary Magdalene, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Saint Paul's Cathedral, 1991-1992 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Save Outdoor Sculpture, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Schlenke, Helen, against Mellon Bank, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Schenley Ballroom, 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Schenley Civic Association against Schenley Hotel Association, 1987-1988 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Schenley Farms, Ad Hoc Committee of, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Schenley Farms, 1985-1987 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Schenley Farms, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Schenley Farms Civic Association, 1989-1996 (Box 6, Folder 4-6)
  - Schenley Farms Civic Association, Holiday Inn, 1988-1990 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Schenley Farms Designation in Oakland Historic District, 1991-1996 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Schenley Farms, Efforts to designate as historic district, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Schenley Farms, Research into Franklin F. Nicola, Schenley Farms realtor, 1983-1991 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Sierra Club, Allegheny County, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Smith, Christopher, Councilman endorses Hill District YMCA dedication, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Society of Architectural Historians, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Soldiers & Sailors Memorial Hall, 1992-1993 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Soldiers & Sailors Memorial site and chronology, 1991-1992 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Steel Industry Heritage Corporation, 1992-1994 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - The 1840s Murray House, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - The Priory, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - The Regent, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - The Twentieth Century Club, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Thrice, Harley, 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - University Club, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - University of Pittsburgh, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - University of Pittsburgh, Master Space Plan Interim Report, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - University of Pittsburgh, O'Connor, President, 1991-1994 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - University Presbyterian Hospital Office, 1990-1991 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Urban Redevelopment Authority merger with City Planning, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Ursuline Center Bloomfield Citizens Council, proposed Ursuline Academy Historic District, 1992-1994 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Washington County Historical Society, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Western Pennsylvania School for Blind Children, 1992-1993 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Westmoreland County Historical Society, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Schenley Farms Historic District architecture and house tour, 1997
  - Handwritten Notes, undated
  - Masonic Temple of Oakland Advertising Suplement to Pittsburgh Press, 1992
  - Correspondence relating to Croghan-Schenley Rooms at the University of Pittsburgh, 1993
  - Schenley Park Bridge rehabilitation, 1993
  - City of Pittsburgh resolution to lease Phipps Conservatory, 1993
  - Phipps Conservatory and Schenley golf Course lease and Jim Ferlo lawsuit, 1993
  - Panther Hollow Bridge Project, Rob Pfaffman letter, 1997
  - Conservatory renovation and historic rooms, 1996
  - Press Relating to Lease of Phipps Conservatory, National Aviary, Pittsburgh Zoo, and Schenley Golf Course, 1991-1993
  - Schenley Park fountains, 1995-1996
  - Western Pennsylvania School for the Blind, article, 1994
  - "A Unique Draw for Downtown," The Pittsburgh Cultural District, 1990
  - Allegheny County Courthouse and Jail, Re-use of, 1994-1996
  - Allegheny County Jail, History, 1995
  - 125 First Avenue Historic Structure Designation Report, 1995
  - Gratchen Haller, "Salt of the Earth" and Letter to Rick Sebak, 1997
  - Draft Design Guidelines Nominated East Carson Street Historic District, 1993
  - Port Authority Mt. Washington Transit Tunnel, undated
  - Smithfield Escarpment Project, 1987-1999
  - Frederick G. Scheibler Jr. Buildings, 1994-1999
  - Murray Hill Avenue Historic District, 2000
  - Young Preservationists of Pittsburgh, 2007-2008
  - Pennsylvania Cultural Data Project, 2006
  - St. Mary Magdalene Church of Homestead, 1992-1994
  - Art Meets History Project, 2008-2009
  - Programmatic Memorandum of Agreement Among PA State Historic Preservation Officer, Advisory Council on Historic Preservation, and US Dept of HUD (DRAFT), 2009
  - Grant Writing Workshop, 2007
  - Demolitions, 2007-2008
  - Manchester Historic District, 2007-2009
  - Market Square Historic District, 2007-2008
  - Active Voice, Interdependent Media, 2006-2007
  - Empowering Neighborhood Organizations, undated
  - The Conrad Project, National Museum of Broadcasting in Pittsburgh, 1998
  - Alpha Terrace, 1994-1995
  - Sunnyledge, 1994-1996
  - River Front Gambling, Press, 1994-1996
  - River Front Gambling, Campaign Against, 1994-1995
  - King Estate, 1990-1993
  - Highland Building, 1991-1994
  - Urban Sprawl and Highway Planning, 1999-2001
  - Historical Architecture Review Board (HARB-CLG) Workshop, 1995
  - Heritage Partnerships, 1995-1996
  - Takings Law, 1993-1996
  - Takings Law, Press, 1995-1996
  - New Urban Agenda Act, 1994
  - Bed and Breakfast Amendment, 1993
  - Mon Valley Expressway, Nine Mile Run, 1997
  - Premature Demolition and Historic Preservation Ordinance, 1996-1997
  - Recommendations for a Revised Historic Preservation Ordinance, 1992
  - Busway Notes, 1997
  - Hillside Committee Mt. Washington, Hillside Presentation, 1998
  - Homewood-Brushton Revitlization and Development Corporation, 1997-1998
  - Houses of Worship in Western Pennsylvania, Arthur Lubetz, 1997-1998
  - 68 Steuben St. Project, 1997-1998
  - Lawrenceville Development Corporation Zoning, 1998
  - Restoration Articles, 1992-1995
  - Fallingwater, Tom Schmidt Retirement, undated
  - Kerotest Building, 1998
  - "The Civil War Fortifications of Pittsburgh: an historical and archaeological survey," William D. McCarthy, 1992
  - Demolition of 5408-5420 Penn Avenue Row Homes, 1998
  - Highland Park Reservoir, 1994-1995
  - WQED - Pittsburgh Neighborhoods Project, 1995
  - Society of Architectural Historians, 1993
  - Beacon Gardens, 1999
  - Save Outdoor Sculpture (SOS), 1993
  - Duquesne Tannery, 1999
  - PBS "Building Big" Documentary Poster, 2000
  - Pittsburgh History and Landmarks Foundation, 1995-1997
  - Pittsburgh History and Landmarks Foundation, 1998
  - Pittsburgh History and Landmarks Foundation, 1999
  - Mattress Factory and the Central Northside Neighborhood Council, 1998
  - Newsletters from other Preservation Organizations, 1997-1998
  - Historic Preservation Data and Documents, 1991-1997
  - Demolition Programs, 1999
  - Lawrence Paint Building, 1999
  - Pittsburgh Wool Company Building, 1999
  - Preservation Alliance, 1999
  - Ritz-Carlton Mt. Washington, 1993-1994
  - 150 Stratford Ave, Neglect, 1993
  - Community Newsletters, 1993
  - Engine House No. 3, 1994-1995
  - Woods House, Hazelwood, 2007-2008
  - Point State Park, 2007-2008
  - Local Agenda 21 Initiative, 1993-1994
  - Bridges Conference, 1995
  - Carnahan-Sellars House, 1995
  - Centre Avenue YMCA, 1994-1995
  - City Council Press and District Map, 1995
  - Committee on Pittsburgh Archaeology and History - Clarion Associates Reports, 1990-1991
  - Committee on Pittsburgh Archaeology & History, 1991
  - Pittsburgh Cultural Trust - Pamphlet and Financial Report, 1994
  - Deutschtown Historic District, 1996
  - Pennsylvania Historical Association (PHA) Annual Meetings, 1991-1995
  - Firstside Preservation Council, Wabash Tunnel, 1996
  - The Lobbying Disclosure Act, 1995
  - Roy Lubove, Article and Obituary, 1992-1995
  - Murphy Oil Soap, "Old Place - New Shine Contest", 1993
  - The Observer Awards, 1994-1996
  - Old House Fair, 1995-1996
  - Partners in Parks, 1995
  - Pittsburgh Neighborhood Profiles, undated
  - "Preservation Education" Newsletter, 1991
  - The Priory, St. Mary's German Catholic Church, 1995
  - "Reclaiming Pittsburgh's Riverfronts: Visions and Strategies" Report, 1995
  - Public Participation in Section 106 Review, 1989
  - Smithfield Street Bridge, 1995
  - Collected Research on Development Sprawl, 1994-1996
  - Steel Heritage Chronicle, 1994
  - Merger of the URA and the Planning Department, 1992
  - Victoria Hall, Lynch Mansion, 1993-1995
  - Grant v. City of Pittsburgh 1996 WL 596905 (3rd Cir (Pa.))
  - Television Program Grant Application, 1996
  - Southside Gateway Project, 1997
  - Rehab Institute Expansion, 1991-1993
  - Fort Pitt Music Bastion Preservation, 2006-2007
  - Sewickley Pink House, 2011-2012
  - Mon-Fayette Expressway, 1998-2003
  - Lowen-Schaffer House, 1991-1996
  - Capital Asset Research Corporation (CARC), 1996-1998
  - Snyder-Bockstoe House, 1991
  - Tiffany Stained Glass Summer Solstice - Calvary United Methodist Church, 2012
  - "'Responsible' Riverfront Redevelopment on the South Side" Report, undated
  - Brochures for Historical Sites and Preservation Organizations, 1994-2000
  - Neill Log House, 1990-1995; 1.
    - Press, 1990-1993 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence, 1992-1993 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Preservation Week 1993 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Preservation Week 1993, Photographs and negatives (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Murphy's Oil Soap "Old Place - New Shine" Clean-Up Project, 1993-1995 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Friends of the Neill Log House 1995 correspondence, agendas, notes, and site plans (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Copies of Neill property sale documents, undated (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Maps and Site Plans, undated (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Research Files, undated (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Katz Business School, 1993-1995; 2.
    - Correspondence, 1993-1994 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Petitions against University of Pittsburgh purchase of Schenley Park land and appended site map for Katz Business School, 1993-1994 (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Press, 1993-1995 (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - Oakland Directions Inc (ODI) Meeting Minutes, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - Copies of Deeds of Sale of Schenley Park to the City of Pittsburgh, undated (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Oakland Civic Center Historic District, 1982-1996; 3.
    - Schenley Farms Historic District City Planning Commission and Historic Review Commission records, 1982-1991 (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - Research Notes on Oakland Historical Significance, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - Draft and final guidelines for Oakland Civic Center Historic District, 1991-1992 (Box 8, Folder 37)
    - Interim Planning Overlay District (IPOD) Records, 1991-1992 (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - Jim Ferlo correspondence relating to Oakland Civic Historic District, 1991-1992 (Box 8, Folder 39)
    - Pittsburgh City Council Resolution Officially Designating the Oakland Civic Historic District, 1991-1992 (Box 8, Folder 40)
    - St. Paul's Cathedral exemption from the Oakland Civic Center, correspondence and press, 1991-1992 (Box 8, Folder 41)
    - Press, 1991-1996 (Box 8, Folder 42)
    - Maps of Oakland Civic Center Historic District and Schenley Farms Historic District, OVERSIZE, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 43)
    - Jim DeAngelis "Oakland: Pittsburgh's Best Hope for the Next Century" and accompanying Pittsburgh Post-Gazette article, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 44)
    - "Oakland Issue Paper: An Urban Design Proposal Executive Summary" by Quick Ledewitz Architects and accompanying letter, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 45)
    - Oakland Neighborhood Alliance, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 46)
    - Western Pennsylvania School for the Blind exemption from the Oakland Civic Center Historic District, undated (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - Mamaux Building
    - Press Relating to Mamaux Building, 1992-1995 (Box 8, Folder 48)
    - Tax Information for Mamaux Building, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 49)
    - Correspondence, 1994-1995 (Box 8, Folder 50)
    - Mamaux Building, Historic Structure Designation, 1994-1995 (Box 8, Folder 51)
    - Action Alerts, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 52)
    - City Planning Commision Agenda and Resolutions Relating to Mamaux Building, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 53)
    - Handwritten Notes, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 54)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 8, Folder 55)
  - Billboard Control Campaign, 5.
    - Research material and material from other organizations, 1987-1992 (Box 8, Folder 56)
    - Press, 1990-1992 (Box 8, Folder 57)
    - Martin Media, 1990-1994 (Box 8, Folder 58)
    - "A Study of Pittsburgh Voter Attitudes Toward Selected Public Policy Issues" conducted for Martin Media, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 59)
    - Committee on Environmental Amenity, reports and meeting minutes, 1992-1993 (Box 8, Folder 60)
    - Pittsburghers for Billboard Control agendas, meeting notices, press releases, 1992-1993 (Box 8, Folder 61)
    - Correspondence, 1992-1994 (Box 8, Folder 62)
    - City Planning Commission and Council Meetings, testimony, minutes, and ordinance, 1992-1994 (Box 8, Folder 63)
    - Jim Ferlo, Billboard Control Campaign papers, 1992-1994 (Box 8, Folder 64)
    - Public hearings, brochures, press releases, 1992-1994 (Box 8, Folder 65)
    - Pioneer Avenue billboards, 1992-1995 (Box 8, Folder 66)
    - Corporate Logos, City Council testimony, press releases, press, and legislation, 1992-2001 (Box 8, Folder 67)
    - Billboard Control Campaign, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 68)
    - Preservation Pittsburgh, correspondence and testimony, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 69)
    - Corporate signage, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 70)
    - Handwritten notes, undated (Box 8, Folder 71)
    - "Legal Considerations and Potential Methods for Regulating Billboards in Allegheny County", undated (Box 8, Folder 72)
  - Pennsylvania Route 28 Expansion, 2000-2008; 6.
    - Press, 1999-2008 (Box 8, Folder 73)
    - Correspondence, St. Nicholas Church and Rt. 28 highway improvements, 2000-2008 (Box 8, Folder 74)
    - St. Nicholas Church press, correspondence, and parish brochure, 2000-2001 (Box 8, Folder 75)
    - St. Nicholas Church campaign, meeting minutes, agendas, and presentation, 2000-2008 (Box 8, Folder 76)
    - Position statements on Rt 28 project, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 77)
    - Canal and stagecoach museum pamphlets, 2004-2007 (Box 8, Folder 78)
    - Legislation, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 79)
    - "Criteria of Effect - Addendum S.R. 0028, Sections A09 and A10 East Ohio Street Improvement Project", 2006 (Box 8, Folder 80)
    - Rt. 28 "Environmental Assessment" and "Criteria of Effect Addendum" on CD, 2006 (Box 8, Folder 81)
    - "PennDot SR 28 Aesthetic Treatments Information Meeting" presentation, 2006 (Box 8, Folder 82)
    - Programmatic Agreement regarding East Ohio Street Improvement Project, State Route 28 A09 A10, 2006 (Box 8, Folder 83)
    - "A Feasibility Study for Pittsburgh's National Immigrant Museum & Trail", 2009 (Box 8, Folder 84)
    - Preservation Pittsburgh suggestions for Route 28 project, undated (Box 8, Folder 85)
  - Howe-Childs Gateway House, 1990-1996; 1993-1996; 7.
    - Project files and legal research, 1990-1996
    - Opinion and Order for Weinberg and Weinberg v. The City of Pittsburgh and the Historic Review Comission No. SA981 of 1990
    - Weinberg appeal, 1995
    - Legal precedence and opinion, 1993-1994
- Fifth and Forbes Development, 1992-2007; 1998-2001; IV.
  - Pittsburgh Register of Historic Places - Central Business District, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - First Side Cultural District Plan, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Pittsburgh Downtown Partnership, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Lazarus Building, Press, 1992-1996 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Lazarus Building, Research, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Lazarus Building, Special Committee Meetings and Correspondence, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Philadelphia - Center City Development, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Board and Strategy Meeting Minutes and Agendas, 1997-2000 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Pittsburgh History and Landmarks Foundation, 1997-2000 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Concept Visuals of Fifth Ave and Market Square from the Urban Development Authority, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Pittsburgh Downtown Plan, Prospectus and CD-Rom, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, 1998-2001 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - F.J. "Jack" Schmitt, Correspondence and Newsclippings, 1998-2002 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Fifth and Forbes Development Plan for PHLF by Ehrenkrantz, Eckstut & Kuhn Architects, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Golden Triangle Parking Zoning Ordinance, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Marketplace at Fifth and Forbes, Promotional Folio, [Oversize], 1999 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Mellon Bank Building, Photgraphs, Negatives, and Postcards, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Brochures, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Handwritten Notes, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Pittsburgh History and Landmarks Foundation, "PHLF News", 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Position Statements on Fifth and Forbes Development, final and draft, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Sala Udin, Newsletters, Correspondence and Press Releases, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Research on State Law and Downtown Development, 1999-2001 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - "Building Blocks of Pittsburgh," Historic Facade Booklet, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - City Council, Form Letter and Petition, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence - City Government, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence - State Government, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Downtown Development Survey, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Downtown Planning Collaborative, Members List, Schedules, Presentations, and Responses, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Handouts, Fliers, Press Releases, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Eminent Domain Amendment Petition, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Fifth and Forbes Conference, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Letters to the Editory - Pittsburgh Post-Gazette, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - "Marketplace @ Forbes and Fifth - Draft Proposal for Housing", 2000 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - "Our Main Street, Our Downtown" Golden Triangle Community Development Corporation Prospectus Booklet and Presentation, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Proposal for the Marketplace at Fifth and Forbes, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Criticism of Historic Review Commission, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Downtown Housing - Press, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Plan C Task Force Revitalization Plan, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Forbes and Wood "Skinny Building," Preservation Proposals and Press, 2001-2002 (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - 5th & Forbes Concept Plan for National Trust Conference (Draft), 2006 (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - "Marketplace at Fifth and Forbes Proposed Sources and Uses of Funds", undated (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Press, Downtown, 1994-1996 (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - Press, "Pro", 1996-1999 (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - Press, "Con", 1998-2000 (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - Press, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - Press, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - Press, Originals, October, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - Press, Copies, October, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 50)
  - Press, November, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 51)
  - Press, December, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 52)
  - Press, January, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 53)
  - Press, February, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 54)
  - Press, March, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 55)
  - Press, April, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 56)
  - Press, May, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 57)
  - Press, June, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 58)
  - Press, July, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 59)
  - Press, August, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 60)
  - Press, September, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 61)
  - Press, October, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 62)
  - Press, November, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 63)
  - Press, 2001-2007 (Box 9, Folder 64)
  - Maps, undated (Box 9, Folder 65)
  - Market Place at Fifth & Forbes, Proposed Sources and Uses of Funds, undated (Box 9, Folder 66)
  - Fifth and Forbes Lighting Project Directory, undated (Box 9, Folder 67)
  - "Questions that need to be answered", undated (Box 9, Folder 68)
- Civic Arena Demolition and Hill District Redevelopment, 2007-2013; V.
  - Work Plans for Civic Arena Advocacy, 2006-2008 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - City Planning Commission Meeting - Handwritten Notes, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Hill Consensus Group Meeting, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Hill District Cultural Resources Conservation Coalition, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Historic Hill Initiative, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 5)